One thing, as you notice we don't have any three point lines here but, that wasn't always part of the game and this court was probably created during, sometime during that period, is the three point line.
The three point line is actually, I talked about it earlier, is nineteen point nine for college and high school, and actually NBA, the NBA line is a little further out, it's at twenty three, nine, twenty three feet, nine inches.
So, whenever you're shooting same shooting mechanics apply.
You want to take your, take your three point shot.
I'm going to show you, I'm going to take, actually go across court here and show you exactly, what a round about what a three point shot would be, being is how we don't have, actually have a three point line on our court.
So, check me out.
When you're coming over here and you're shooting a three point shot, same shooting mechanics apply as a regular shot, no changes, you just might, down here you probably want to shoot a jump shot, unless you're strong enough to actually get it there with a set shot.
So, when you're taking a, taking your three point shot, you want to make sure if you're playing outside, outdoors, you got to allot for the wind, that's the thing about playing outside.
You've always got to allot for the wind.
So, if you're taking this a little more distance, so when you're shooting the three point shot, you allot for the wind and there you go just like that, you take the shot.
So, same shooting mechanics apply and there you have it, shooting the three point shot.